punjabnewsline.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy

This statement describes what you can expect from us regarding personal data on  Punjabnewsline.com, and your associated rights and responsibilities. This statement is a part of  the Punjabnewsline.com user agreement but trumps any conflicts with the agreement. This  statement does not address anyone else's practices or our practices beyond the  Punjabnewline.com site.

We respect your privacy and consider it an important element of our business. We do not collect  personal information about you when you visit our website(s) unless you volunteer to provide that  information to us.

 **Special Note About Google Advertising**

 Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using  cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other  sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As  mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to  Google's own privacy policies.

 **About Google advertising:**

What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used  by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users  visit an AdSense publisher'??s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped  on that end userâ??s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense  publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out  of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. (link  to: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html )

 **Email-Only Registration.**

You may subscribe to emails or newsletters by providing only your email address and password and mobile number(if demanded), which we use to create a username and account for you. For privacy purposes, an email-only account acts like a registered account.

 **Registration/Member Data.**

When you register, you provide us with some personal data (including your email address and mobile number). You can also tell us more about yourself through your account pages or through site  features such as Wish Lists. Occasionally, a co-brand partner may provide us with data about you.  We use registration and member data for many purposes, including to target ads to you and to email  you (including newsletters and alerts). In most cases, you can configure your account to turn these  emails on and off. However, some administrative emails (such as emails about user agreement changes  or communications) are not optional while you have an account.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Our website(s) has links to other website(s) in the World Wide Web. The privacy policies of these website(s) is not under our control. Once you leave our servers, use of any information you provide  is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. It is advisable to  read their privacy policies for further information.

 **Content and Ratings.**

You can publish reviews and comments. As an unregistered visitor, we may allow you to rate products and/or reviews. Your member name is automatically displayed with reviews and comments you publish,  and if other members choose to, they can receive email notifications of your publications or  publish their own comments to your reviews.

 **Email Tools.**

If you send emails to or through Punjabnewsline.com, your email will include your email address and any personal message you include. However, these emails aren't private communications. We do not retain, in any easily-retrievable way, the addresses you are emailing. You may not use these tools to send spam or content that violates the user agreement.

 **Data Changes.**

If you terminate your account or delete/change your data or content, we usually update our live databases immediately. To do this, please edit your Member Profile. However, some data may update more slowly, and some old data may remain in our archives and records. Also, we may be unable to propagate changes to partners who receive your data or content. If your account is being terminated or suspended, we may maintain some data to prevent re-registration.

 **Government Relations and Lawsuits.**

We may disclose data about you to the government agencies if we are required to do so or if we think the disclosure is appropriate, and you authorize these disclosures. We may also disclose data about you in connection with actual or potential lawsuits (a) if we are required to do so, (b) if such disclosures may potentially mitigate our liability, or (c) to enforce our rights.

 **Notification of Changes**

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Web site. We will post our new privacy policy, along with the date of its last revision, prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this Web page for information about revisions to our privacy policy.
